I once had a dream where I was a falcon.
My eyes were new, fresh, vision like
nothing before.
I could see in what felt like four
dimensions and time was one of them
explored.
I could now see everything.
Unbounded from the ground, I was let
loose. The higher I soared, the more
free I became.
The sky was all mine and I was the same.
I am the fastest animal on the planet.
To naked eyes, a blur.
Swipes of red, [music] white, silver,
and black would occur without alert.
Prey would have no time to pray.
In this dream, my body was a [music]
falcon, but my mind was still mine. I
could recognize my city and nest from
miles away in detail without trying.
All dreams feel real, of course, but
this one was different still. A bouncing
word I heard upon waking [music] even
now gives me chills.
Until no sound,
I could still see [music] everything as
it is and was, but now I'm flying on the
ground.
A new
red
rush.
>> [laughter]
>> That was an incredible Three stacks is
undefeated. How did they get him to do
that? That's the question.
>> Andre 3K, Atlanta native, narrating that
incredible
piece of poetic video from the Falcons
as they show off their new red rush
uniforms in which Atlanta is considering
Boy, look at that.
>> on next year, but your last name
wouldn't be Tay O. Well, but it is this,
Tay
It is this, Tay O. Tay O, baby. Here's
the real helmet that they sent us cuz
the Falcons are the most generous. Yeah.
What do you think about the combo? Well,
first of all, the combo between Andre
3000 and that movie? I sit high up on my
nest and I could recognize my city from
miles away. What? That's great, but no
time to pray. Like it was just so poetic
how you hear Andre 3000 doing his thing
and then you see Bijan spinning and oh,
bro.
>> Hey. Bravo, Atlanta Falcons.
>> a game.
>> If you're only going to make an
introduction to a brand new uniform,
they have some culture behind it. That's
how you do it. You'll get one of the
greatest of all time. Mhm.
Ooh. Atlanta.
Bro, I DIDN'T EVEN PLAY FOR ATLANTA. I
PLAYED FOR THE RIVAL AND I WAS LIKE,
"OH, THIS is hype, boy." Oh [laughter]
my gosh.
>> bro. Look at that.
>> So, Tamera, what you got? I love the I
love the numbering on the jersey. I
think the numbering is fire. I love a
black helmet. I think the black helmet
is fire.
Big logo on the side.
>> Yes. Wish they put a stripe. Stripe
would have really finished it off, but I
think it's fire.
>> Keeping it clean. Well done, Falcons.
Excellent look.
This is the kind of hook we need in
March, whatever, April, whatever it is.
And uh really How many days until we
play a game?
>> The bar is high.
>> Bar is real high.
>> Like the nest that he was talking about
in the Look at that. And then the
Falcons coming down the building in
Buckhead and just
Man. Man. Man. Now, this is the question
though, okay? Is there certain helmets
that wouldn't look good in matte?
Because right now, every helmet that I
saw in matte is
looks matte as heck.
I don't love a white matte. That's I
like the shiny white. That's true. stuff
swinging it around like a bag. Let's try
it on, man. Let me put THIS HELMET ON.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW THE WAY THAT YOU GOT IT,
MAN.
>> [laughter]
>> GET OUT OF THE WAY. OUT OF THE WAY.